higamecenter.com 2017-12-04

# Privacy Policy

 ChromeAppGames has adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain how ChromeAppGames collects, stores, and uses the information collected in connection with ChromeAppGames's Services.  

###  1.Information Collection and Use

 By using our services, You agree to this privacy policy and give an explicit and informed consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with this privacy policy. 

 ChromeAppGames is a website providing free games, We doesn’t handle personal or sensitive user data, ChromeAppGames is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

###  2.Information we get from your use of our services

#####  * Log Files

##### 

 We may log IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

#####  * Local Storage

##### 

 We may collect and store information locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5, Flash) and application data caches. We use these data to store the services state such as game levels or scores. 

#####  * Cookies and similar technologies

##### 

 We and our partners use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit our web site, and this may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify your browser or device. We also use these technologies to collect and store information when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services. 

###  3.Privacy Policy Changes

 Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page.
